(Episode 12)
You've been here before, haven't you?
We weren't able to reach you
since we didn't have your contact.
Why?
Please see your doctor. He's still here.
What is going on?
What?
I think you have leukemia.
Leukemia is...
You know what it is.
Do you have any family members
who had this?
This disease most likely
runs in the family.
I see.
I heard my father passed away from it.
It is cancer, isn't it?
Are you sure I have that?
I'll be sure once you get reexaminations.
Miss, get off.
I think I need to go to Seoul.
My mom left being so mad.
I need to comfort her.
Okay.
I will take you.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
I see.
How long do I have to see Eun Seo?
For how long are you going to meet her?
Tell me. For how long?
How long do I have to see her
reflected in your eyes?
Tell me.
Say something.
Isn't it enough for you?
Isn't it enough for you that I'm with you?
Then, let's go to the U.S.
when this semester is over.
What do you think?
Is this still not enough?
Once we go there,
we won't ever come back here.
What about this?
Is this still not enough for you?
You mean your heart will be with her.
You just can't tell me
that you'll love me with your heart.
You are the one I chose.
That's all I can say, Yu Mi.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter.
It does not matter.
I won't ever let you go.
I will not let you go,
no matter what happens.
I will be back soon.
Yu Mi.
It's just two months.
We're going to the U.S. in two months.
I will give you a ride.
Be careful.
And don't work too hard
on your business trip.
Don't worry. It's only for a week.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
I'll drive you to the airport.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Okay, let's go.
Eun Seo, what brings you here?
Didn't you go to work today?
No.
Why not? What's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
You guessed that so easily.
I got a cold.
Did you? Let me see.
I think you have a fever.
Eun Seo, why don't you lay down on my bed?
What is this?
Why is there so much food?
It's been a while since I came home early.
Do you have money to waste?
I'm sorry. It's just for today.
And...
What is it?
Mom, let's have a drink together.
What?
I love it.
You can't even drink.
I can drink.
- For you, Mom.
- Okay, fill it up.
It's good.
Dad.
Your father?
How long did it take before he passed away
after the diagnosis?
Why are you asking that?
I'm just curious.
Because he died before I was born.
Was it soon?
I'm not sure.
I can't remember it for sure.
Was it longer than two months?
It took a while.
Also, it took a lot of money.
Was he that bad?
He really was.
He used to break things
almost all the time.
He was a drunkard and a gambler.
He was the worst.
The reason for his dying
from that disease was,
I think, a form of punishment.
I see.
He got punished.
Dad also got punished.
What are you talking about?
No, it's nothing.
Mom.
I have made you upset, haven't I?
After you sent Sin Ae away,
you were upset while you raised me, right?
There are far more things I did wrong...
than I did well, while raising you.
What are you saying?
You haven't done anything wrong.
I wish I had been with you
since I was born.
No way.
Your other mom would wail
upon hearing that.
No.
It would have been better...
if I had lived with one family
since I was born.
It would have been good for you...
and also good for the other mom.
There wouldn't have been
this much regret on my part.
Are you...
still thinking of your brother?
No.
It's so bitter.
Mom, do you want to sing together?
My pale pink skirt is
Fluttering
In the spring wind
Biting my dress string
Again today
On the village shrine road
Visited by spring maidens
When the flowers bloom
We laugh together
When the flowers fall
We cry together
With that sweet vow
Spring days are gone
Jun Seo.
How could I...
not think of you, even for a second?
I can't, right?
Yes, I have about two months left.
Yes, once I go to the U.S. this time,
I don't have plans to ever come back.
I will visit you before I leave.
Yes.
It's just two months.
We're going to the U.S. in two months.
Stop smiling. You'll grow on me.
Don't smile when you're leaving
for the U.S. soon.
Did Yu Mi come?
I don't think she's coming.
She's planning to get her injured hand
examined while in Seoul.
I think she'll come today or tomorrow.
Is that so?
Isn't it a good thing that
she keeps checking her hand?
I hope things turn out well.
They will.
(Check Account Balance)
(Please enter your four-digit PIN.)
My eyes hurt since I watched movies
all night again.
Did you rent movies again?
Because of the guy at the rental store.
Why do you like him?
Dimples, a blue shirt, and ripped jeans.
He is gorgeous.
I think he is my first love.
I don't think that is love.
Why not?
It's not love.
They say that if it's true love,
you don't need any reasons.
Is that so?
It's not like that in the movies.
- Kang Hee.
- Yes.
Among sad movies,
is there a movie in which
the main character dies?
There are a lot of them.
"Love Story," "Take All of Me,"
"The Letter," and "Christmas in August."
What other ones are there?
Do they all die from cancer?
Most of them do. Why?
Then,
in the movie,
does it say how much it costs
to treat cancer, by any chance?
Do I need surgery to live?
That is the only option at this point.
Right.
I see.
First of all, you need to rest.
Be careful not to get bruises.
Also, be careful not to bleed,
and watch out for tartar on your teeth.
You may have intermittent bouts of pain.
When you experience pain,
come straight to the hospital.
And...
How much will it cost for the treatments?
I am not sure.
It could be tens of thousands of dollars.
What did you say?
Tens of thousands of dollars?
Choi Eun Seo.
What's going on?
What?
You're fired as of today.
What? I am fired?
I think it's
Director Han Tae Seok's order.
Don't you know that?
Who is this?
Are you Choi Eun Seo?
Tae Seok.
I told you not to call me like that.
Are you that stupid?
Am I fired?
How could you do it without any grounds?
Do you think only you can do
whatever you want, but I can't?
This is me.
Aren't you happy not to see me anymore?
Aren't you?
Tae Seok.
Look at me.
I'm not your plaything.
I've been thinking.
About what could be
the most valuable thing to you.
And funnily enough, it's money.
If so, that is my strongest asset.
Why did I take such a long way
to get here?
Love? Don't be ridiculous.
I will buy that. I will pay for it.
How much is your love?
How much do you think?
How much can you afford?
I...
need money.
I really need money.
How much can you offer me?
How much can you pay me?
How much can you pay?
How much should I charge you for me?
Mom.
Why did you come home this early?
Aren't you feeling well?
Did you leave work early?
I quit.
What? Do you quit?
Get over here. Come here.
When you dump the rich man,
you should work to make money.
No, Jong Chul.
How ungrateful you are.
Stop, Jong Chul. Stop hitting me.
You can't hit me, Jong Chul.
I shouldn't get bruises anymore,
Jong Chul.
Jong Chul, stop it.
Get out of my way.
Don't you want to get beaten?
Then, go out and make money.
No, please.
I really shouldn't get bruises, Jong Chul.
Jong Chul, please.
Eun Seo, run away while I hold him.
Why won't you come here?
- Jong Chul.
- Get out of my way. Let me go!
Get out of my way!
Are you going to where your fiancé is?
Yes, I'm going to the airport now.
I'm glad you have good news to tell him.
What?
That means...
Your test results came out really well.
I believe your hand will get better enough
for you to paint.
Is that true?
Is it, doctor?
Thank you.
Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
I'm sorry I came here.
Yu Mi is not here.
She went to Seoul.
It's okay even if she's here.
This is my home.
You are good at lying.
Come on in.
Just a second. I'll clean it up.
Do you have two months
before you leave for the U.S?
Did you know that?
Yes.
Jun Seo.
During the two months,
can we meet like this sometimes?
I won't ever get to see you
once you leave.
Can we meet without telling anyone,
for just a few times?
We cannot, can we?
We can't.
We can't do that.
We shouldn't.
Did you come to say that?
No.
Actually, I had a fight
with my brother again.
I think it became a habit
to come here when I had a fight.
Eun Seo.
It's fine. I didn't get beaten.
I can't cut it.
It's done.
Aren't you cold, Eun Seo?
Wait for a second.
No, Jun Seo.
Take this.
We can't see each other again
before you leave.
Right?
I'll be back.
Don't come back.
I know you're not going to come back.
Don't come back,
and don't reach out to me.
You should just assume,
"She's doing well here."
Just assume that.
Eun Seo.
You should think, "She's doing well here."
Think of me like that.
Please just think of me like that.
Can't you do that?
I will.
I'll think of you, Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
During the two months,
can we meet like this sometimes?
It got colder.
Yu Mi.
What are you doing?
Jun Seo, you need to wear warm clothes.
It got cold.
You don't have a proper jacket.
Where is the jacket?
Which one?
You know my favorite.
The black one with a hoodie.
That one.
Did you take it to a dry cleaner's?
No.
I gave it to Eun Seo.
She came by earlier.
She had only thin clothes.
I see.
You can't even lie.
I hate you for that.
You could've lied for something like that.
I would lie if I were you.
By the way,
I went to the doctor.
He said my hand wouldn't recover.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
I am so sorry, Yu Mi.
It is all right.
It doesn't matter if I can't paint.
Instead, you'll be my hand.
It's okay.
Everything is fine.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
I can't give you this.
Why not?
Because it is an anticancer drug.
I can't give it to you
without a doctor's prescription.
Is it an anticancer drug?
An anticancer drug would be...
used for treating cancer, right?
You need to wait for your turn.
You cannot come in like this.
What is going on?
- Leave, please.
- Who are you?
Does she have cancer?
Does Eun Seo have cancer?
Where is it?
It's all right.
I was going to quit, anyway.
It's fine.
You came to apologize to me, didn't you?
There is no need to apologize.
Compared to what I have done to you...
I will get punished, won't I?
Give me a chance.
Give me one more chance.
Tae Seok?
Give me a chance.
Tell me three reasons you love me.
Then, I will give you a chance.
I don't have any. I can't think of any.
That's why you can't get a chance.
You will never get one.
That's too bad.
If you had even one reason,
I would have considered it.
You will never get another chance.
I won't ask you to marry me.
I won't bother or bully you.
I won't ask you to love me.
Your disease,
let me help you beat cancer.
I will fix your disease.
When you beat cancer,
when you get well,
I...
will leave you.
I won't stick around stubbornly,
I'll leave you.
So, please let me get it cured.
How did you know?
How?
You can't die.
I won't forgive you if you die.
Promise me.
When you get well, tell me.
"Tae Seok,"
"I don't love you."
"So, please leave me alone."
Promise me.
So, please give me a chance.
No.
I can't.
How can I ask you to do that
after all this?
I can't.
Is this the cancer clinic?
Yes, do you have any rooms available?
Is this Na Rae Nursing Home?
Yes, what's the location?
Mom.
Was Dad in pain?
Did he suffer immensely?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you keep asking about him?
It's nothing.
I wish he hadn't been in much pain.
How could that be possible?
He said it was better to be dead
than to have that pain.
He was also such a crybaby,
so it was an ordeal.
I see.
How long was it before he was in pain
after the diagnosis?
I don't know. I don't remember.
Eun Seo, are you sick?
What?
Why are you sweating so much?
What's wrong?
It's been a long time.
Yes, it has.
How is Yu Mi?
She's doing well.
She went to Seoul.
Isn't it strange?
I thought I would never find you.
But I missed you the most
when in dire times.
Dire times?
Did something happen to you?
Actually, I haven't decided...
whether to tell you or not.
What is it?
Is this about Eun Seo?
No.
I heard you're going to the U.S.
Yes.
Once you get to the U.S.,
don't look back at what happened here.
Don't look back.
Tae Seok.
Eun Seo,
please look after her.
Jun Seo.
Drink this.
Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
Do you really need to go to the U.S.?
Can you live with me...
just for six months?